today's date see 8th of November and
2016 now we've been playing around with
her what is it a fiend out Touareg
tutorial 13 2013 model yeah do you know
what what what have you noticed it moves
it moves fun it moves very quickly so
just surprisingly quickly and this is a
diesel diesel yeah
diesel doggy but it's a diesel rocket
now it's diesel rocker ok so we we just
we just been out and we'd shorted the
cell actually which is disappointing we
got it down to eighteen point seven
three miles and miles per gallon so that
was a little bit disappointing but we
fixed it so we've just refilled it and
we've zeroed have me yes okay so it's
all ready to happen so you know the
routine on your way I'm gonna let you
know how it goes okay fine